myonlinetraininghub.com 2015-06-08

# Privacy Policy • My Online Training Hub

**My Online Training Hub Privacy Policy**

Read very carefully:

**Introduction**

My Online Training Hub regards customer privacy as an important part of our relationship with our customers. The following privacy policy applies to all My Online Training Hub users, and conforms to Internet privacy standards.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact us at [privacy@myonlinetraininghub.com](mailto:privacy@myonlinetraininghub.com)

My Online Training Hub only contacts individuals who specifically request that we do so or in the event that they have signed up to receive our free newsletters or have purchased one of our products.

**Collection of Information**

My Online Training Hub collects personally identifying information from our users during online registration and online purchasing. Generally, this information includes name and e-mail address for registration to receive our free newsletters and name, postal address, and credit card information when purchasing our products. All of this information is provided to us by you.

All correspondence may also be collected and stored, particularly in regard to sales, support and accounts, including Email.

**Use of Collection Information**

This information is used for internal marketing purposes only. My Online Training Hub does not sell, exchange, or release your personal information (name, e-mail address, mailing address, credit data, etc.) Your information is not shared with any other third party or company outside of billing and shipping purposes.

Any details collected from My Online Training Hub customers are required in order to provide you with our products and/or services, and a high level of customer service.

All of the newsletters that are sent to you by My Online Training Hub include an unsubscribe link in them. You can remove yourself at any time from our newsletters by clicking on the unsubscribe link. You can also contact us at [privacy@myonlinetraininghub.com](mailto:privacy@myonlinetraininghub.com) to change your information at any time.

**What are cookies/clear GIFs and how do we use them?**

Cookies: Like many other commercial sites, our Site utilizes standard technologies called “cookies” and clear GIFs to collect information about how our Site is used. A cookie is a small data text file, which a website stores on your computer’s hard drive (if your web browser permits) that can later be retrieved to identify you to us. Cookies were designed to help a website recognize a user’s browser as a previous visitor and thus save and remember any preferences that may have been set while the user was browsing the site. A cookie cannot be read by a website other than the one that set the cookie. A cookie cannot pass on a computer virus or capture any of the Personally Identifiable information.

Clear GIFs: At times, we work with third-party service partners that employ clear GIFs (also known as pixel tags, single pixel GIFs, web beacons or action tags) for our benefit to help us measure advertising effectiveness. Clear GIFs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of our users. The main difference between the two is that clear GIFs are invisible on the page and are much smaller, about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. Clear GIFs are not tied to your Personally Identifiable Information and only track the visitor traffic and behaviour to and on our Site.

Clear GIFs can “work with” existing cookies on a computer if they are both from the same website or advertising company. That means, for example, that if a person visited “www.companyX.com”, which uses an advertising company’s clear GIF, the website would match the clear GIFs identifier and the advertising company’s cookie ID number, to show the past online behaviour for that computer. This collected information can be shared with the advertising company. We do, at times, provide such information to our third-party advertising service partners, but that information can only be used by our partner for our benefit and never includes personally identifiable information.

**Storage of Collected Information**

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card numbers) on our website, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). When Credit Card details are collected, we simply pass them on in order to be processed as required. We never permanently store complete Credit Card details.

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it.

If you have any questions about security on our Website, you can email us at [privacy@myonlinetraininghub.com](mailto:privacy@myonlinetraininghub.com)

**Access to Collected Information**

If you would like to update the information on our database you can logon and update your profile in the Members Area, or contact us at [privacy@myonlinetraininghub.com](mailto:privacy@myonlinetraininghub.com) and we can do it for you.

**Orders**

If you purchase a product or service from us, we may request certain personally identifiable information from you. You may be required to provide contact information (such as name, Email, and postal address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date).

We use this information for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you.

**Third Parties**

My Online Training Hub may at its discretion use other third parties to provide essential services on our site or for our business processes. We may share your details as necessary for the third party to provide that service.

These third parties are prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for any other purpose.

My Online Training Hub does not share any information with third parties for any unknown or unrelated uses.

**Legal**

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Website.

**Links**

Links on the My Online Training Hub site to external entities are not covered within this policy. The terms and conditions set out in this privacy statement only cover the domain name of www.myonlinetraininghub.com

**Changes to Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by Email, or by means of a notice on our homepage.

**My Online Training Hub Security Policy**

My Online Training Hub uses the eWAY Payment Gateway for its online credit card transactions. eWAY processes online credit card transactions for thousands of Australian merchants, providing a safe and secure means of collecting payments via the Internet. All online credit card transactions performed on this site using the eWAY gateway are secured payments.

• Payments are fully automated with an immediate response.

• Your complete credit card number cannot be viewed by My Online Training Hub or any outside party.

• All transactions are performed under 128 Bit SSL Certificate.

• All transaction data is encrypted for storage within eWAY’s bank-grade data centre, further protecting your credit card data.

• eWAY is an authorised third party processor for all the major Australian banks.

• eWAY at no time touches your funds; all monies are directly transferred from your credit card to the merchant account held by My Online Training Hub.

**For more information about eWAY and online credit card payments, please visit[www.eWAY.com.au](http://www.eway.com.au/ "eWAY")**

**Delivery Policy**

After ordering online, you will receive an email confirmation from eWAY containing your order details (if you have provided your email address). We will normally confirm receipt of your order within a few minutes of ordering.

If you wish to query a purchase please contact us at [sales@myonlinetraininghub.com](mailto:sales@myonlinetraininghub.com)

**30 Day Money Back Guarantee/Refund Policy**

At MyOnlineTrainingHub.com we want you to know that your purchase is 100% risk free.  If for any reason you decide you want a refund, simply email us at [refunds@myonlinetraininghub.com](mailto:refunds@myonlinetraininghub.com) within 30 days of signing up and we will promptly refund 100% of your money, guaranteed.

**Cancellation Policy**

You can cancel your subscription at any time, by simply emailing us at cancellations@myonlinetraininghub.com.  Please allow 3 days before your renewal date to ensure you are not automatically charged for the next month.
